Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one, so
let's let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending,
so let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake
up, heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, is waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride
away, we're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun,
while our dreams are never-ending.
So let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake
up, heartbeat, we will be one, go hey!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you Can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
Huh?
Did I hear a gunshot over there?
Are you all okay?
What happened to Traffy?
You still with us, Luffy?
Tell us what's going on, please!
Sorry about all the commotion, folks.
Forgive me.
This is the pirate and
warlord, Trafalgar Law.
He's the culprit behind
the false report of
my abdication from the
throne this morning.
He was attempting to pull
me off the big chair.
But fear not.
I've taken care of the problem.
That all makes sense now!
So his intent was to throw Dressrosa
into a spiral of chaos, Your Majesty?
I'm so relieved!
We're safe now!
Hey, Mingo!
You're gonna pay for doing that to Trophy!
Listen, kid.
You'll mind your own damn business
if you know what's best for you.
Don't you know, Law used to work for me.
I'm just cleaning up my own mess.
Team, get Traffy out of
here! Leave it to me!
Hey, Vice Admiral!
The pirate hunter's on the move!
Should we nab him?
Hmm, sounds good.
Wait, just a moment.
Hey, come on, talk to us!
Please, tell us what's going on!
With heavy heart, I'm sad to
report Sir Law has fallen!
Shut down by Doflamingo!
What? Hear that?
Not good?
The pirate hunter Zoro
and Foxfire Kinema, right?
I saw Momonosuke earlier, too,
unguarded aboard your ship.
Don't listen to that bastard.
We would never let him take Momo.
I never doubted you.
It's you.
I guess you could call it second sight.
But there's something that's telling me.
Not answering you would be
better for both our sakes.
Zoro!
Sir Zoro!
What happened to Zoro, Kin'emon?
Sir Zoro just vanished!
Kin'emon!
I'm gonna help you!
Oh, yeah, that's Sea
Prism Stone, isn't it?
Hey, Keenemon, are you okay?
Come on, answer me!
Don't tell me that you're dead!
Vice Admiral!
Now treacherous.
A long-range sword attack.
I can't believe that
old blind gambler turned
out to be a Navy Admiral
this whole time. That guy!
Thank you for your help before.
I fear I may seem ungrateful
turning my blade on you as I am,
but I do not intend to be callous.
Fate can be a cruel and
ironic mistress at times.
This man, who stands here
alongside Doflamingo,
is a Navy Admiral.
It would see what, what?
Wait—so there's a navy admiral
just hanging out and dress rosa.
Then
perhaps that means doflamingo is
allied with the navy in that event?
We could have countless enemies to face.
Wake up, please, sir!
Law—are you kidding me?
Both of them can fly—how are you?
how are you Faring!
Please answer us!
Let's have a chit-chat back
at the palace, Fujitora.
If I can convince you
to cooperate with me,
you'll have their heads in no time at all.
I shall listen to what you
have to say, oh heavenly demon.
But the decision remains my own.
Captain Roro no Zoro at once!
Looks like our cover's blown, huh?
Yes, that seems to be the case.
That'd be our cue to go!
Truffie!
This is Keenumont speaking.
Unfortunately, they have seized Sir Law.
Hey, Luffy, you should
go and locate an exit.
We'll stay on the move and hold
out as long as possible for you.
I'm on it! Let's hurry!
I heard Traffy say
something after he got shot.
He might still be okay.
Not you guys too!
What's going on?
What?
Just spit it out already!
There they are!
Damn it.
They spotted us.
We have a big dilemma!
It's a massive pirate ship!
And it belongs to Big Mom!
Jimmy! Jimmy!
What is one of the Four Emperor's
ships doing here on your way?
Are there figureheads singing somehow?
Are you sure?
Is she attacking you now?
We're all gonna die!
What's up?
You actually see her on the ship?
Can't confirm that, but I do see those
two weirdos from Fishman Island, though.
Mama, confirming that
we have located Caesar.
Oi, they have been hostage
just as we speculated before.
Let us send them on our bon voyage by
seeking the ship to recolor Monsieur Caesar.
Oh, great!
Now we're dealing with Big Mom, too?
Damn it, Luffy, you shouldn't
have picked a fight with her!
Seems like they're here for Caesar.
Caesar?
Why are you so popular
every damn place that we go?
Did they come to rescue you, too?
They're here to kill me, surely!
I am begging you, I don't want
to be captured by Big Mom!
Please, it'll be the end of me!
Look, I stole research
funds from her, okay?
You did what?
Well, skip the details,
it's not important.
The point is, if they found out
I stole from them, I'm done for.
Do you really think I
care if you live or die?
Well, lucky for you,
our whole plane is screwed if we
hand you over, so shut up, okay?
Hang it open, fire on us!
We're getting pushed further
and further away from just Rosa.
Think we can shake him off?
Everything okay?
Hey, listen,
I don't think it would be a good idea
to leave an emperor back to Dressrosa.
It'll just throw the whole
kingdom into mass hysteria
and knock the whole Bito
Flamingo plan out of whack,
you know?
Come to think of it, why is
Caesar back on the sunny?
Was it not obvious the
deal crumbled apart?
Why else would Traffy have
gotten his ass beaten, huh?
Yeah,
we're stuck with him because Law told
us to take him to the next island,
unfortunately.
I'm with Franky on this one.
I don't think we should take
him anywhere near Dressrosa.
Listen, Sanji, I'm not saying
this because I want to run away.
There are three main things that
Doflamingo and us are fighting for.
Caesar, the Smile Factory, and
for some reason, Momonosuke.
We obviously haven't completed our
mission to destroy the factory yet,
so he's got one.
But fortunately, we have the other
two pieces right here with us, get it?
Traffy sacrificed himself and
fought Doflamingo as a decoy
so we could move these two
things away from his reach.
I believe he was also trying to buy us some
extra time for the factory plan as well.
He put himself through all that
just to help give us an edge.
Now if we go back just to make it easy
for Doflamingo to snatch the two of them,
then his sacrifice will
have been for nothing.
Gotcha.
Good point.
And we'll just have to take
Traffy back at all costs!
What's the name of the next island again?
That would be Zoe.
Saji!
Nami!
Chopper!
Brooke!
Mama!
You guys move on ahead and go!
Well, if that's what you
want, roger that, Captain.
But, one request first.
What is it? Nothing.
Just permission to fight back.
I want to launch a counterattack
against Big Mom's ship.
Sure, why not? What?
No way.
I already started that fight anyway.
True that.
That's way too dangerous.
Please, don't!
Alright, everyone.
We'll see you in zone.
Got it.
Don't worry.
You can leave all the
factories smashing up to us.
All of you stay safe, okay?
We're going to head
straight for the palace.
Yes, and then we'll beat
the hell out of Doflamingo.
Sorry, kid, that's my barrier.
The heck are you doing here?
Is that Bartolomeo?
Our fight is none of your business.
Sorry, were you fighting?
I just put up a barrier because
I felt like it, honestly.
I was given an order by the young master.
If you get in my way, I'll kill you, too.
You can try.
But good luck breaking my barrier
with those little baby kicks.
What do you want?
I'm in the middle of something here.
Curb the attitude, Dellinger.
I was going to ask if you were done with
Bellamy, but it seems you're still at it.
You're too slow it's not my fault.
I got interrupted
It's fine.
Just finish him later!
Duffy has a new order for you.
Go guard the toy house with Lao
Ji and his group on the double.
Come on Diamante.
I'm almost done here
Just give me a second.
He'll be good and dead.
No way
A new order, and it's true.
He really does want me dead.
Screw this crap.
And screw you two!
Get out of my way!
Let me kill him.
I am going to stop him dead.
Now, move!
You kidding?
I'm not budging an inch.
You don't want your boss
getting mad, do you?
So just go already!
You and your barrier can go to hell!
This isn't over by a long shot!
Mark my words, you're not
leaving Dressrosa alive!
Yeah, yeah, that's what they all say.
That was Diamante on
the transponder snail.
So everything Della just said was true.
That means Doflamingo was the
one who was lying all this time.
He was toying with me, so I
just gotta win the tournament,
then you'll give me a spot in the family!
Of course.
I'll be cheering for you.
Good luck out there
Let me take you to the
medical world, buddy. Damn it!
I don't need you butting it!
Just go away!
Leave me alone!
I've lost my only reason to live!
Why the hell do you want to
save me in the first place, huh?
We were enemies!
I would have killed you along with
everyone else in that battle royale!
Now you're protecting me! Yep.
We may fight in the same ring.
They become like brothers.
We're comrades in battle now.
And dammit, I'd never
turn my back on a comrade.
Now you know the dark
history of this nation.
And next, I shall tell you how
I plan to liberate its people.
What do I call this plan, you ask?
Operation Dressrosa S .O .P.
S .O .P., huh?
So what does that stand for?
Beneath this kingdom, there is
a massive underground network.
Unbeknownst to the people above,
there lies a trade port for black market
dealings, as well as a mysterious factory.
There, the captured Tontara,
along with the humans who have
been transformed into toys,
are forced to work around the clock.
Okay, cool.
But what does SLP mean again?
We'll sneak in through
an underground passage
that we've been digging
for an entire year.
Then, we'll rescue everyone.
We'll wreck the facilities.
And defeat the Doflamingo family.
Then, King Rick will return to the throne.
That is the goal of our operation.
I doubt it'll be quite that easy.
Of course there may be complications.
After all, none of us can predict
what might happen in Dres Rosa.
especially in its current state.
That said, there is one thing
we must do if we want to win.
The one who turned us into toys is a
member of Doflamingo's inner circle.
We'll target them and shut down the
power of their Hobby Hobby fruit.
Hobby Hobby what?
We simply have to knock them out.
And doing so will break
the spell on the toys?
That's correct.
All of the toys will return
to their human forms,
in the secret factory
and the streets alike.
Then, the lost memories of them will
come flooding back to their loved ones.
While that's a victory in itself,
it's hard to say what will follow.
How many of the former toys
will rise up in arms with us?
What will the citizens
think when their memories
are restored and what
action will they take?
How will Dol Flamingo respond?
How will the Navy respond?
The only thing that we know for certain is
that the kingdom will
be thrown into chaos.
So this person with the hobby hobby
power, the one who changed everybody,
where are they now?
They must be pretty strong, huh?
According to our Tontara scouting unit,
she should be in the underground
trade port for the time being.
She's a special officer
in the Treble Army.
Her name is Sugar.
She is a girl who can transform anything
into a toy simply by touching it.
She appears to be a child,
but it seems that anyone
who eats the Hobby Hobby
Fruit stops aging the moment
that its power takes hold.
Since she's such a vital figure,
she is under the constant
protection of Treble,
one of Doflamingo's
highest officers. I see,
but we can avoid a conflict with Treble
just as long as we can knock out sugar.
That's correct.
The plan is to scare her out of
her wits and make her pass out.
Operation Sugar Oversurprised Bannock!
And that is the meaning behind
SOP, my inquisitive friend. Ow!
Now that's the kind of
name I can get behind, bro!
If it's a little girl
we're fighting, no problem!
Follow me!
Alright, I'm getting all fired up.
Franky Aresolat in the house!
You dick my combat hair!
Yay, Fraland!
Yay, Usaland!
You guys are the best! Aw, yeah!
Usaland is gonna save the day!
Ain't no plan too grand for Fraland! Wow!
Now take us to the underground, little
dudes, cause we are ready to go!
Yeah, Usaland guys!
Meanwhile,
Luffy runs from one passage to the next,
frantically searching for the
exit to the Corridor Coliseum.
Hold on.
Forget the exit.
Where am I?
So the plan is, someday,
I'm going to be Mr.
Luffy's apprentice.
Well, it's more like my dream.
Oh, the bathroom!
Huh?
Roosterhood, it's me!
And am I glad to see you! Ah!
M-m-mister Luffy!
Pull it together, Baratie! Mr.
Luffy's gonna be the king of the pirates!
You gotta make a better
impression than this!
Oh, it's Bellamy!
He's too radiant.
It's like staring at the sun.
Hey, Mr. Luffy.
I don't remember what happened.
Did you get to see Mr.
Zoro?
Yeah, I sure did.
Thanks for the help.
It was my pleasure.
Anyway, I gotta get somewhere quick, see?
But I can't find the exit.
Think you can help again?
There is no exit.
You have to keep on fighting.
Hold on. Bellamy?
Why are you so beat up?
Never mind that.
I'm telling you, there's no escape from
this place unless they want you to leave.
You might as well stop
looking and give up hope.
There's no way out. How?
There was a way in.
It's an emergency.
You work for Doflamingo, right? Come on.
Please, you gotta know a secret way out.
You work for Doflamingo?
I wasn't even good enough to be as flunky.
Bellamy!
My friends need my help!
I'm looking to get out
of this place myself.
If you follow me, maybe
you'll get out too.
But no promises!
Really? Thanks, buddy!
Glad you're showing me the way!
I'm not showing you a damn thing!
I just won't stop you, that's all!
You're not telling me to
betray my boss, are you?
Even now...
I'm loyal to Doflamingo!
No matter what I'll always respect him,
come on, man, just a second ago, you?
I don't care.
I've got my own honor to uphold.
That's fine.
I'll follow you out.
but wait what about the
flame flame fruit mr.
Luffy there's one guy I hope
doesn't win but it's fine.
the lives of my friends matter way more.
don't worry!
I'll take care of that for you.
in fact, that was my plan
from the very start of.
I knew you'd want a keepsake
from your dear departed brother,
so I was going to win it
and then give it to you.
Really?
Do you mean it?
Of course!
It was destinable.
Uh, you're getting hard to understand.
Don't you worry about nothing.
Just go and save the day and let old
Bartle take care of the tournament for you.
Why are you telling that to the wall?
Thanks!
You're awesome, buddy.
If you think you're getting the
flame flame fruit, you're wrong.
Sorry, Luffy. It's mine.
Oh, yeah? You want to fight? Listen up!
I don't know who the hell you
think you are, but that's Mr.
Luffy to you, you damn punk!
The Flame Flame Fruit belonged
to his brother, Firefist Ace,
so nobody deserves to
have it more than him.
Also, he's going to be King of
the Pirates one day, you jackass!
I know.
I've known that for years.
You're facing the moment of truth now.
Rebecca, you get to
the finals at any cost.
Right.
This moron's pissing me off.
He got a grudge against Mr.
Luffy or what?
Look, you're upsetting him, you jerk!
Luffy?
You got out of the damn place.
Why are you crying?
What do you mean you can't
find the pirate hunter?
He was right here.
Call the vice-admiral.
Hurry. Yes, sir.
It seems my flawless disguises have fooled
the Navy into thinking we're not but toys.
Flawless, my ass.
Look how much we stick out.
These costumes are weird.
But I chose all the
best animals, like carp.
Carp are great.
Stop crying already.
You want to save Traffy or not?
I'll save Traffy.
And I'll kick Mango's ass.
Now I know the Flame Flame
Fruit will be in good hands.
What does that mean?
I heard Robin's in Dressrosa, too.
Oh, it's been forever.
Hope I can see her.
I'm glad you got to see Luffy.
Yeah, I was afraid he
was going to punch me.
Are you crying? What?
I don't cry.
You're wondering if you
could have saved him.
If you'd been there too?
Let me know as soon as you have
more info on this underground place.
Okay.
In the meantime...
I'll be taking back
that fruit for you, Ace.
Luffy and I will carry on your will.
I never thought he might still be alive.
Who the hell are you talking about?
I was sure he died.
Almost years ago.
He was out there.
Thank you for listening.